--==圣城家园SCG字幕组 http://hd.cnscg.com/==--
仅供翻译交流使用, 禁止用于商业用途
协调：心仪
翻译：死神夜月 Mabb Storm89
校对：心仪Sally
Enjoy a Cup of Fresh Coffee.
新鲜咖啡 欢迎品尝
It's hormonal.
都是荷尔蒙的缘故
I mean, I don't usually fall back on.. It's women's issues.
我是说 我不是在推卸责任 但这是她的问题
But child-proofed how? Gates and stuff?
你们怎么来保护孩子? 是装安全门还是怎样?
Dude,she did the drawers.
老兄 她自己做的抽屉
We don't even know if this whole fertility thing's gonna work..
我们还不确定她能不能生下来呢..
she's screwed in these little jobbies where you can't even open the drawers.
她不知做了什么手脚 抽屉根本打不开
At all?
一点也打不开?
No. They open an inch, then you gotta dig your finger in.
不是 能打开一英寸的小缝儿 手指能勉强伸进去
- It's a nightmare.  - I guess sooner or later...
- 真难想象  - 我觉得迟早...
Yeah,a lot later. She did the upper cabinets.
是啊 已经晚了 她还做了上橱柜
Kid will be 30 before he can reach them,assuming we have a kid.
即便我们有孩子的话 也得等他到30岁才能够得着
It is natural for her to feel protective.
保护孩子是母亲的天性
Don't even... You have women's issues.
别这么说... 你不也有这样的问题
Please. You of all people.
得了吧 你们这些人
Oh, come on. It's a jinx.
这可不是好兆头
It guarantees that we won't get pregnant.
在这样下去 我们连孩子都没有
And it takes me about 20 minutes to get a fucking beer.
我花了20多分钟才将啤酒取下来
Guys. Guys!
伙计们 伙计们!
Stockholm went south.
斯德哥尔摩（瑞典首都）出问题了
Seriously? I thought they were looking good.
真的假的? 我看他们挺好的啊
What cracked?
发生什么了?
I haven't seen the footage. Word's just going around
我还没看录像 现在谣言满天飞
Well,that's never been a stable scenario.
那本来就不是一个保险的方案
Everyone knows you can't trust Swedes.
大家都知道不能相信瑞典人
That means there's just Japan. Japan and us.
那就意味着只剩下日本人了 日本和我们
It's not the first time it's come down to that.
这又不是第一次了
Japan has a perfect record.
日本一直做的很好
We're number two. We try harder.
我们只能排名第二 我们得加把劲
If we fail, then...
如果我们失败了 那...
Please. We haven't had a glitch since '98.
摆脱 从98年以来 我们什么时候出过错
We know what we're doing, Lin.
林 我们知道该怎么做额
Or we have it written down... somewhere.
至少我们把步骤也都记下来了嘛
You guys better not be messing around in there.
你们最好别在里面乱搞啊
Does this mean you're not in the betting pool this year? Big money.
难道说你不参加今年的赌钱游戏了么? 那可是有一大笔钱呢
I'm just saying, it's a key scenario.
我只想说 这个方案很重要
No, I hear what you're saying.
好吧 我知道了
In '98, it was the chem department's fault, right?
98年那次是化学部门弄砸的 对吧?
Where do you work, again? Wait. It's coming back to me, now.
你在哪儿工作来着? 等一下 我想起来了
It's gonna be a long weekend if everyone's that puckered up.
如果大家脾气不好 那周末就不好过了
So you wanna come over Monday night?
那你周一晚上能来我家吗?
I'm gonna pick up some power drills. Liberate my cabinets.
我得找把电钻 解放我的柜子
Are you even listening to me?
你在听我说话吗?
Professor fuckwad.
狗屁教授
Why haven't you stuck that asshole's picture on the dartboard yet?
你怎么不把这个混蛋的照片钉在飞镖靶子上呢?
It's not that simple. Oh,my God!
没那么简单 哦 天呐!
- Your hair. It's blonde.  - Very fabulous,no?
- 你的头发 变金黄色了  - 是不是很棒 对吧?
- I can't believe you did it.  - But very fabulous,right?
- 真不敢相信你会染成这个颜色  - 但很不错 是吧?
Hurry up with the "very fabulous." I'm getting insecure about it now.
快说"很棒"  我现在都不太确信这样好不好
No,it looks awesome. Curt's gonna lose it.
不 棒极了 科特会喜欢的
Curt's gonna thank me. And so will you...
科特会感谢我的 你也是...
while we're burning this picture.
当我们把这张照片烧掉的时候
Not ready.
等一下
Seriously,this isn't his fault.
说真的 这不是他的错
What's not his fault?
什么不是他的错?
Fucking his student or breaking up with her by email?
跟自己的学生上床还是发邮件跟她分手?
I knew what I was getting into.
我知道自己要面对什么
Oh, please.
拜托
You know what you're getting into this weekend?
你知道你这个周末会面对什么吗?
This.
这个
And if Holden's as cute as Curt says he is...
如果霍顿 如科特描绘的那般帅的话...
possibly getting out of it.
或许这还能派上用场
That is the last thing that I want.
这是我最不想要的了
If you treat this like a setup, I'm gonna have no fun at all.
如果你是想设计我俩 那就没意思了
I'm not pushing...
我没在逼你...
but we're packing this!
但我们得带上这个!
Which means we definitely won't have room for...
我们真没地方放...
what if I get bored?
万一我无聊了呢?
These will help?
这些管用吗?
Soviet Economic Structures? Aftermath of the...
苏联经济结构? 什么什么的余波...
No! We have a lake and a keg.
不行! 我们得到湖边喝酒呢
- No more learning!  - Think fast.
- 别再学啦!  - 接着
Faster than that.
反应还得快点
Sorry. Sorry. Move along.
对不起 对不起
- Nice!  - Is that Holden?
- 漂亮!  - 他就是霍顿吗?
We'll be right down. He just transferred from State.
我们这就下去 他刚从州立大学转过来
Best hands on the team. He's a sweet guy.
队里最好的球手 人也很不错
And he's good with his hands.
他手法也很不错
I'm kinda seeing this girl...
你好像和我约会的女孩...
but you're way blonder than she is.
但你的头发比她黄多了
But I was thinking, you know,maybe.. What is this?
我在想 你知道 也许... 这是什么?
What.. this? What are you doing with these?
这是什么? 你那这些做什么?
Okay,I get it. I'll leave the books.
好吧 我知道了 我不带书了
No,who gave you these? Who taught you about these?
谁给你这些的? 谁教你这些的?
I learned it from you, okay?
我跟你学的 知道了吗?
I learned it from watching you!
都是跟你学的!
Seriously, Professor Bennett, he covers this whole book in his lectures.
说真的 班尼特教授的讲座 包含了这本书所有的内容
You should read this.
你应该读读这个
Gurovsky. Now this is way more interesting.
戈罗夫斯基 这本有趣多了
Also, Bennett doesn't know it by heart..
还有 班尼特不懂这本书...
so he'll think you're insightful.
所以他会觉得你很有见解
And you have no pants.
还有 你没穿裤子
Oh, shit!
哦 该死!
- That pretty much it?  - Fucking better be.
- 东西都带上了吗?  - 妥妥儿的
You know, Jules, it's a weekend, not an evacuation.
你知道的 朱尔斯 这是度周末 不是去逃难
Trust me when I say there is nothing in those cases...
相信我 我敢说我箱子里带的东西...
you won't be glad I brought.
都用得上的
I'm shutting' right up.
看来我得闭嘴了
Oh,my God.
哦 天哪
Marty!
马蒂!
Fuck is wrong with you, bro?
哥们 你他妈的是怎么了?
People in this town drive in a very counterintuitive manner.
镇上开车的人都不跟着感觉走
That's what I have to say.
这就是我想说的
Do you wanna spend the weekend in jail?
你想在监狱度过周末吗?
We'd all like to check out my cousin's country home.
我们是要去我表兄弟在乡下的住处
Honey, that's not okay.
亲爱的 这样可不好
Statistical fact...
统计表明...
Cops will never pull over a man with a huge bong in his car.
警察不会让一个拿着大烟斗的男人停车的
Why?
为什么?
They fear this man. They know he sees further than they...
他们怕这样的人 他们知道这种人不像他们看起来那样...
and he will bind them with ancient logics.
他们会装作看不到
Have you gone gray?
你染发了?
You're not bringing that thing in the Rambler.
你不能把这东西带到车上
What?
什么?
A giant bong in your father's van?
这么大的烟斗放在你爸车里?
What are you, stoned?
你怎么了 药药多了吧?
Hey, man.
嘿  伙计
Dana, you fetching minx!
丹娜 迷人的小妞!
You have any food?
有吃的吗?
- Everybody ready?  - Yeah!
- 各位都准备好了吗?  - 当然!
- Yeah?  - Okay, I'm ready!
- 真的?  - 准备好了!
Let's get this show on the road!
上路出发!
Nest is empty. We're right on time.
全家出动 时间刚刚好
I hope this is the right road.
希望这条路没走错
It doesn't even show up on the GPS.
GPS上没有这个地方
It is unworthy of global positioning.
这里不值得全球定位
That's the whole point. Get off the grid, right?
这才是重点 远离喧嚣 对吧?
No cell phone reception...
没有手机信号...
no traffic cameras.
没有交通摄像头
Go someplace for one goddamn weekend where they can't...
去一个GPS都找不到...
globally position my ass,man.
我们的地方
This is the whole issue.
这才是重点
Is society crumbling, Marty?
社会解体了吗 马蒂?
No. Society is binding. Right?
不 社会在束缚我们 不是吗?
It's filling in the cracks with concrete.
到处是钢筋混凝土
Everything's filed or recorded or blogged, right?
所有的事情都会被存档 对吧?
Chips in our kids' heads so they won't get lost.
在孩子脑子里植入芯片 以防他们走丢
Society needs to crumble.
社会需要瓦解
We're all just too chicken-shit to let it.
我们只是太胆小 不敢让此发生
I've missed your rants.
我会怀念你这些豪言壮语的
You will come to see things my way.
总有一天你会知道我是对的
Identification, please.
身份证 先生
Mr. Sitterson.
是希森特先生
- Mr. Hadley.  - Thank you.
- 哈德利先生  - 谢谢
- What's your name?  - Daniel Truman,sir.
- 你叫什么名字?  - 丹尼尔・杜鲁门 长官
This isn't the military. You can drop the "sir".
这里不是军队 不用称呼"长官"
But Sitterson does like to be called "ma'am."
但是西特森喜欢别人叫他"夫人"
- Or "honey toes."  - He'll also answer to "honey toes."
- 或者是"甜心"  - 他也会回应"甜心"的
You clear on what's gonna be happening here?
你知道要发生什么事了吗?
I've been prepped. Extensively.
已经准备好了 请放心
Did they tell you that being prepped is not the same as being prepared?
他们和你说过这次跟以往不同么?
They told me. I'll hold my post, Mr. Hadley.
说了 我会履行好自己的职责的 哈德利先生
Good man.
好样的
Okay. System's online.
好的 系统连线
Acquiring target. Let's see what we got.
搜索目标 我们瞧瞧他们长啥样
I'm thinking this thing doesn't take credit cards.
我想这东西肯定不能刷卡
I don't think it knows about money.
我觉得他们连钱都不认识
I think it's barter gas.
我们应该用物品来换油
Hello?
有人吗?
Hey, Holden.
嘿 霍顿
- Holden!  - I don't think there's gonna be...
- 霍顿!  - 我想这里不是...
- You come here uninvited?  - Fuck!
- 你不请自来?  - 该死!
Sign says "closed."
上面写了"停业"
Yeah, we were looking to buy some gas.
是的 我们想买些汽油
Does this pump work?
这个还能用么?
If you know how to work it.
如果你知道怎么用的话
We also wanted to get directions.
我们也想问一下路
We're looking for... What's it called?
我们在找... 叫什么来着?
Tillerman Road. Do you know if it's this way?
舵工路 你知道怎么走吗?
Tillerman Road takes you up the hill, there.
舵工路会通往山顶 在那边
Dead-ends at the old Buckner place.
老巴克纳是尽头
My cousin bought a house up there.
我表兄在那里有房子
You go through a mountain tunnel, there's a lake.
你穿过山区隧道 那有个湖
- Would that be the...  - Buckner place.
- 那里就是...  - 巴克纳
Always someone looking to sell that plot.
总有人想卖掉那地方
You knew the original owners.
你认识那地方之前的主人
Yeah, not the first.
是的 但不是最初的
I seen plenty come and go. Hell, I been here since the war.
我看过很多人来来去去 见鬼 从战争时 我就在这儿
- Which war?  - You know damn well which war!
- 哪场战争?  - 明知故问!
Would that have been with the blue and some in gray?
是蓝灰战争吗?
Brother, perhaps, fighting against brother in that war?
兄弟之战 也许是?
You sassing me, boy?
你敢对我无礼 小子?
You were rude to my friend.
你先对我朋友无礼了
That whore?
那个妓女?
- What'd you say?  - I think we got enough gas.
- 你再说一遍?  - 我们油加够了
You got enough to get you there.
去那里是够了
Getting back...
回来...
that's your concern.
那才是你们该担心的
Well, good luck with your business, sir.
祝你生意兴隆啊
I know the railroad's coming through here any day, now.
听说铁路很快会穿过这里
That's gonna be big.
规模很大的噢
Streets paved with actual street.
到时这里会有真正的街道
Fucker.
傻帽
Guys, take a look.
伙计们 瞧
This must be it.
就是那儿了
Oh, my God. It's.. beautiful.
哦 天哪 太漂亮了
One spider and I'm sleeping in the Rambler.
如果有一只蜘蛛 我就会车里睡
I mean it.
我说真的
Come on. Give me a hand.
来吧 帮我个忙
This is awesome.
太棒了
It is kind of cool.
真酷
You gonna kill us a raccoon to eat?
你能给我们抓个浣熊吃吗?
I will use its skin to make a cap.
我会用它的皮做个帽子
Everybody get your suits on. In 10 minutes, we're heading to the lake.
大家把泳衣穿上 10分钟后 我们去湖边
Yeah.
太好了
I was not informed there would be calisthenics.
我之前都不知道 这里还能跳健美操
Yeah, I don't think so.
是啊 我也没想到
Whoa.
哇哦
No way.
不是吧
Ah, shit.
啊 该死
This is happening.
真的发生了
Hold up!
别脱了!
You've gotta be fucking kidding me.
你开什么玩笑
That's just creepy.
太诡异了
It was pioneer days.
在拓荒时代
People had to make their own interrogation rooms.
人们必须做个审讯室
Who did your cousin buy this place from?
你表兄从哪里买的这房子?
We should check the rest of the rooms, make sure this is the only one.
咱们应该检查一下其余的房间 确保不会有这种事儿发生
Cause you know Marty wants to watch us pounding away.
你知道的 马蒂想看我们床战的
I didn't even like hearing that.
我都不稀得听
How about we switch?
要不我们换个房间如何?
Not that I'd...
我并非...
I mean, I'd put the picture back but you might feel better if we switched rooms?
我是说 我可以把画挂上 但你可能换房才能安心
I really would.
这样最好了
Thanks. For being decent.
谢谢你 真绅士
It's the least I could do...
应该做的...
since Curt and Jules sold you to me for marriage.
科特和朱尔斯希望咱俩结婚
They're not subtle.
他们并不明智
Well, I'll just be flattered and keep it to myself.
好吧 我只是觉得受宠若惊了
Yeah, I'm not looking for...
我并不想找...
But, I'm still grateful that you're not a creep.
但 我很庆幸你不是个变态
Hey, let's not jump to any conclusions there.
嘿 别这么早下结论
I had kind of an internal debate about showing you the mirror.
我也考虑了很久 要不要偷窥你
Shouting on both sides. Blood was spilled.
挣扎的都内出血了
So, you're bleeding internally?
这样你就内出血了?
Pretty bad.
糟透了
Well, Jules is pre-med. You should probably talk to her.
朱尔斯是学医的 你该找她看看啊
Okay.
好吧
Wow.
哇哦
Yeah, I don't think so.
我可不想这样
Places everyone.
各就各位
We are live.
我们在现场直播
Engineering, we got a room change.
工程部 我们有一个房间被改动了
Polk is now in two, McCrea is in four.
丹娜在2号房间 霍顿在4号房间
Operations, do you copy? We need a scenario adjustment.
运营部 收到了吗? 我们需要改动一下方案
Miss Lin.
林小姐
We've got the blood work back on Louden. Her levels are good.
我们找到了朱尔斯的血液 她身体状况不错
But we're recommending a fifty-milligram bump..
但是我们建议使用50毫克Rhohyptase
of Rhohyptase to increase libido.
来增加性欲
- Sold.  - Do we pipe it in, or do you wanna do it orally?
- 好的  - 你想注射还是口服?
Ask me that again, only slower.
再问我一次 慢点说
You're a pig.
你真是个猪
Guess how we're slowing down cognition.
猜猜我们怎么降低认知力的
I don't know.
不知道
The hair dye.
染发剂
Dumb blonde. Very artistic.
金发傻妞 有意思
Works its way into the blood,through the scalp. Very gradual.
通过头皮会逐渐进入血液吸收
Chem department keeps their end up.
化学部工作干得不错
I'll see it when I believe it.
眼见为实
- Control?  - Yeah, go ahead.
- 控制台吗?  - 是的 说吧
I have the harbinger on line two.
2号线有人要跟你通话
Oh, Christ. Can you take a message?
哦 上帝 能让他留言吗?
I don't think so. He's really pushy.
恐怕不行 他催的很紧
To be honest, he's kind of freaking me out.
说老实话 我都有点怕他了
Okay. Put him on.
好吧 接进来吧
Mordecai, baby, what's happening? How's the weather up top?
莫迪凯，宝贝，怎么了? 上面天气怎么样?
The lambs have passed through the gate. They are come to the killing floor.
现在羊已入虎口了 进入屠宰场了
Well, you're doing a great job out there.
好的 干的漂亮
By the numbers, man. You got us started off just right.
伙计们 按顺序进行 你这开头很好
So, we'll talk to you later, okay?
我们晚点再谈 好吗?
Their blind eyes see nothing of the horrors to come.
他们还没意识到 接下来的是多恐怖
Their ears are stopped.
他们什么也听不进去
They are the God's fool.
真是愚蠢
Well, that's... how it works.
那... 该怎么做
Cleanse them. Cleanse the world of their ignorance and sin.
干掉他们 让他们的愚昧和罪恶从这个世界消失
Bathe them in the crimson of...
让他们身上沾满血腥...
Am I on speakerphone?
你开免提了?
No. Absolutely not.
不 没有
Speakerphone, no. No, I wouldn't do that.
免提 不 没有 我没开
Yes, I am. I can hear the echo.
不 你开了 我听见回声了
Oh, my God. You're right. Hang on one second,I'll take you off.
哦 天哪 你说的没错 等一下 我把免提关了
That's rude. I don't know who's in the room.
太无礼了 我都不知道谁在屋子里
Fine. There. You're off.
好吧 免提关了
Thank you.
谢谢
Don't take this lightly, boy.
别掉以轻心 伙计
It wasn't all by your numbers.
这不是你能决定的
The fool nearly derailed the invocation with his insolence.
这些蠢货差点破坏了祷告
The ancient ones see everything.
祖先们都看着呢
And they will not be...
他们不会...
I'm still on speakerphone, aren't I?
你还开着免提 是不是?
Oh, my God. Mordecai.
哦 天哪 莫迪凯
I can't believe it. I did it again!
真难以置信 我又把免提打开了!
Mordy?
莫迪?
What happens next?
接下来会怎么样?
Oh! That's cold!
哦! 太冷了!
How cold? Is it worth it?
有多冷? 我能下去么?
Come on, Jules. Life is risk.
来吧 朱尔斯 生命在于刺激
Yeah, I might just risk lying out in the sun for a while.
是啊 也许我可以冒险晒晒阳光
Boo.
晕
- Hey, what is that?  - What?
- 嘿 那是什么?  - 什么?
In the lake, right there.
在湖里 就那儿
- Oh, come on.  - No you guys, I'm serious. Right there.
- 别逗了  - 不 伙计们 我认真地 就在那儿
There! There! God, looks just like my girlfriend!
那! 就是那! 天哪 看起来像我女朋友!
Oh, my God!
哦 天哪!
There's something else in the lake!
湖里还有其他东西!
- It's a gorgeous man!  - I'm gonna kill you!
- 是个帅哥!  - 我要杀了你!
Don't kill the gorgeous man! We're endangered!
别杀帅哥啊! 我们都要灭绝了!
All right. Last chance.
好的 最后一次机会
It's post time. Dig deep, people. Betting windows are closing. Okay.
下注时间到了 下注吧 伙计们 投注快要结束啦 好的
Okay, who's still out?
还有谁没下注
Let's see. We got engineering, we got R&D, and we got electrical.
我看看啊 下注的有工程部 研发部和电气部
Did you see who they picked?
知道他们选谁了么?
They're practically giving their money away.
实际上他们在浪费钱
You should talk, Aquaman.
你还敢说呢 潜水侠
- What do you mean?  - Ah,nothing.
- 什么意思?  - 没什么
Okay, all right.
好吧
I'm not even sure we have one of these.
我记得咱们没这个
Zoology swears we do.
我发誓咱们有动物学部门
They'd know. Okay. All right, people.
他们会知道的 好的 伙计们
Hey, what do you got?
你赌哪个了?
No, they've already been picked.
不行 他们已经被选了
What? No. Who took them?
什么? 不会吧 谁选他们的?
Maintenance.
维修部
Maintenance? They pick the same thing every year.
维修部? 他们每年选的都一样
What do you want from me?
你想让我怎样?
If they were creative, they wouldn't be in maintenance.
如果他们富有创造力 就不会在维修部了
You're gonna have to split this if you win. You wanna switch?
如果你赢了就要和他们分奖金 想换吗?
I don't know, I don't know. What do you think?
不知道 我不知道 你觉得呢?
More than anything, I just want this moment to end.
重要的是 我只想这事快点结束
Not betting?
不下注?
Not for me. Thanks.
不了 谢谢
Seems a little harsh,doesn't it?
看起来挺没节操的 是吧?
It's just people letting off steam.
只是宣泄而已
This job isn't easy,however those clowns may behave.
工作压力是大 不过这种胡闹确实有点过了
Does the director...Do they know about this downstairs?
主管... 他们知道下面是这样的吗?
The director doesn't care about this stuff.
主管才不关心这些事呢
As long as everything goes smoothly upstairs.
只要上面一切正常就好啦
as long as the kids do as they're told.
只要孩子们都听话
But then it's fixed.
模式不都是固定的吗
No,no,no.
不 不 不
How can you wager on this when you control the outcome?
结局都是由你们操控 还有什么好赌的?
No,we just get 'em in the cellar. They take it from there.
不 我们只是引他们进入地窖  接下来还是看他们自己
No,they have to make the choice of their own free will.
不 他们将按照自己的意志作出选择
Otherwise the system doesn't work.
否则系统不会运作
It's like the harbinger.
比如说那个先知
It's this creepy old fuck,practically wears a sign,"You will die."
老掉牙的惊悚套路 典型的警告 "你们都会死"
Why do we put him there? The system.
干吗要放这么个人呢? 这是规定
They have to choose to ignore him..
他们必须选择忽视他
and they have to choose what happens in the cellar.
他们必须自己在地窖选择将要面对的东西
Yeah,we rig the game as much as we need to.
我们只在必须的范围内控制游戏进程
but in the end,they don't transgress.
但是到最后 只要他们不越界
They can't be punished.
那他们也不会受到惩罚
So what's it gonna be,Truman?You in? Window's closing.
怎么样 杜鲁门? 要加入吗? 就要截止了
I'm fine.
算了
Okay.
好吧
That's it,gang!
好的 伙计们!
The board is locked!
下注截止了!
Oh,let's get this party started!
喔 开始狂欢吧!
Let's get this party started!
开始狂欢吧!
There you go.
干杯
Okay,my turn.
好吧 该我了
Jules
选朱尔斯
Truth or dare?
真心话还是大冒险?
Let's go dare.
大冒险
All right.
很好
I dare you to make out with..
我命令你去跟...亲热一下
Please say "Dana," please say "Dana."
"跟丹娜" 快说"跟丹娜"
That moose,over there.
跟那边那个麋鹿
Marty
马蒂
have you ever seen a moose before?
你见过麋鹿么?
Whatever that mysterious beast is.
那么 那怪兽是个啥?
That's a wolf.
那是狼
I'm living in a,leave me alone.
好吧我大麻抽多了 行了吧
Jules
那么朱尔斯
I dare you to make out with that wolf.
我命令你跟那只狼亲热一下
No problem.
没问题
Who?
谁?
Me?
我?
Well,yes,I am new in town.
嗯哼 是呀 我刚搬来不久
How did you know?
你怎么知道的?
Oh,my God.That is so sweet of you to say.
噢 天哪 你嘴巴可真甜
I just colored it,in fact.
实际上 刚刚染的呢
No,no,no.
不 不 不
There's no need to huff and puff.
没必要压抑自己
I'll let you come in.
我会让你爽的
Thank you.
谢谢
Yeah.
耶
Now,...
接下来嘛...
Dana
选丹娜
Truth.
真心话
What's that supposed to mean?
这算什么意思?
I'm just skipping ahead.
直奔结果而已
You're gonna say dare.
你会说大冒险
She's gonna dare you to do something you don't like..
她会命令你去干你讨厌的事情
and then you'll puss out and say that you wanted truth all along.
然后你会使小性 说我本来就想选真心话
Really?
真的吗?
Okay,Jules.
好吧 朱尔斯
Dare.
大冒险
What the hell was that?
怎么回事
It's the cellar door.
那是地窖的门
The wind must've blown it open.
风吹开的吧
That makes what kinda sense?
什么情况?
What do you think is down there?
你们觉得下面有什么?
Why don't we find out?
干嘛不下去看看?
Dana
丹娜来吧
I dare you.
我命令你
How long do I have to stay down here?
我得在下面待多久?
Oh,you know,just 'til morning.
噢 你知道的 到天亮就行啦
Dana
丹娜
You okay?
你没事吧?
Yeah.
还好
Sorry,I just scared myself.
不好意思 自己吓到了
Well,you called for help. That voids the dare.
嗯 你求助了 大冒险失败
Take your top off.
脱上衣吧
What?
怎么了?
I don't make up the rules.
规矩又不是我定的
Oh,my God.
噢 上帝啊
Look at all this.
瞧瞧这些
Guys...
伙计们...
I'm not sure it's awesome to be down here.
我觉得下到这来是个错误
Guys?
伙计们?
Dude,seriously,your cousin is into some weird shit.
哥们 说真的 你表兄的可真不是一般人啊
I'm pretty sure this ain't his.
我确定这些可不是他的
Maybe it was the people who put in that mirror thing.
说不定是装镜子的那些家伙弄的
Some of this stuff looks really old.
有些物件看起来有年头啦
It's beautiful.
真美
Maybe we should go back upstairs.
我们还是回上面去吧
I dare you all to go upstairs.
我命令你们全部回上面去
Guys?
伙计们?
Guys,listen to this.
听这个
"April fourth.
"四月四日
"Father was cross with me and said I lacked the true faith.
"父亲生我的气了 他说我没有真诚的信仰
"I wish I could prove my devotion..
"我真心希望我可以证明我的虔诚
"as Judah and Matthew proved on those travelers."
"像犹大和马太向那些旅行者证明一样"
What is that?
那是什么?
Diary of Anna Patience Buckner, 1903.
安娜・佩先斯・巴克纳的日记 1903年
"Mama screamed most of the night.
"妈妈整夜都在嚎叫
"I prayed that she might find faith..
"我祈祷希望她已找到了信仰
"but she only stopped when Papa cut her belly...
"但她只是停止了尖叫 因为爸爸剖开了她的肚子...
"and stuffed the coals in.
"还填了些煤块进去
"Judah told me in my dream...
"梦里犹大对我说...
"that Matthew took him to the black room,so I know he is killed.
"马太带他进了黑屋 我知道他已经被杀了
"I want to understand the glory of the pain like Matthew...
"我试图像马太那样体验荣耀之痛...
"but cutting the flesh makes him have a husband's bulge...
"但是切割肉体让他勃起...
"and I do not get like that."
"我可不想那样"
- Jesus. Can we not?  - No. Go on.
- 上帝啊 别念了吧?  - 别 继续念
- Why?  - I want to know.
- 干吗啊?  - 我想知道结果
"I have found it...
"我终于找到了...
"in the oldest books,the way of saving our family.
"从那最古老的书中找到了拯救我家人的方法
"My good arm is hacked up...
"我的左手被砍掉了...（这厮左撇子）
"and et,so I hope this will be readable.
"所以 希望右手写的还能被人读懂"
"That a believer will come and speak this to our spirits.
"能被某个信徒念出来让我们的灵魂听到
"Then we will be restored and the great pain will return."
"那时 我们将重生 荣耀之痛也将回归"
And then there's something in Latin.
然后下面是用拉丁文写的
Okay,I'm drawing a line in the fucking sand,here.
好了 这是我的底线了
Do not read the Latin.
别读那些拉丁文
What the fuck?
什么声音?
- Dolor...  - No, no.
- 疼痛...  - 别 不要
- Stop being a fucking baby.  - Curt!
- 别像个小孩一样 - 科特别这样
It's a diary.
只是本日记
It doesn't even mean anything.
不会有什么事的
- Dana!  - "Dolor supervivo caro.
- 丹娜!  - "Dolor supervivo caro.
"Dolor sublimis caro.
"Dolor ignio annivos."
We have a winner!
获胜者出炉!
It's the Buckners, ladies and gentlemen!
他们选了巴克纳一家 女士们先生们!
The Buckners pull a 'W'.
巴克纳一家获选
All right. That means that congratulations go to Maintenance!
好的 那就是说祝贺 维修部
Who share the pot with Ronald the intern.
与实习生罗纳德共享奖金
Yeah!
耶!
That's not fair. I had zombies,too.
这不公平 我也选了僵尸
Yes,you did. You had zombies.
没错 你是选了 你选了僵尸
But this is "Zombie Redneck Torture Family," see?
但这是"受折磨的农民僵尸家庭" 看到没?
They're entirely separate species.
完全不同种类的
Like the difference between an elephant and an elephant seal.
就好像大象和海象之间是有区别的一样
There's always next year.
别气馁 明年再战
They're like something from a nightmare.
他们像是来自于梦魇
No. They're something nightmares are from.
不 他们才是梦魇的根源
Everything in our stable is remnant of the old world..
所有我们的库存都来自于旧世界的残留
courtesy of you-know-who.
拜那谁谁所赐
Monsters. Magic.
怪物 魔法
Gods.
众神
You get used to it.
你得习惯它
Should you?
你已经习惯了?
Oh,man. I'm sorry.
好了 兄弟 我很遗憾
- He had the conch in his hands.  - I know.
- 他都把海螺拿在手里了  - 我知道
A couple more minutes,who knows what might've happened?
时间上差了一点点 世事难料啊?
I am never gonna see a merman. Ever.
我永远也看不到人鱼怪了 永远
Dude,be thankful.
哥们 庆幸吧
Those things are terrifying.
那玩意太麻烦了
And the cleanup on them is a nightmare.
清理起来才真是噩梦呢
So, the Buckners.
嗯 巴克纳一家
Yeah,well,they may be zombified,pain-worshipping,backwoods idiots..
嗯 好吧 僵尸 自虐狂 郊外的傻X
But they're our zombified,pain-worshipping,backwoods idiots.
但那是我们的僵尸 自虐狂 郊外的傻X
With a hundred percent clearance rate.
百分百的清除率呢
True. So should we call Japan?
这倒是 给日本打电话?
Tell them to take the rest of the weekend off?
告诉他们可以好好享受剩下的周末了?
Yeah,right. They're Japanese. What are they gonna do? Relax?
是 没错 那是日本人 他们能干啥? 歇着?
I'd just like to see them fall on their asses,for once.
我只是想看他们栽个跟头 哪怕一次
Oh,God,don't even joke.
噢 天啊 可别这么说
Every other branch has air-balled.
其他分支都搞砸了
We need the Japanese crew to get it done. There's too much riding on this.
日本人最好别出岔子 责任重大啊
Fuck, yeah, baby.
真棒 耶 宝贝儿
This is so classy.
真上档次
Come on,like you wouldn't want a piece of that.
得了 好像你不动心想咬她一口似的
Can we not talk about people in pieces any more tonight?
今晚别再谈什么咬人的事 好吗?
Are you feeling lonely,Marty?
觉得被冷落了 马蒂?
Marty and I were sweeties in our freshman hall.
刚入校的时候马蒂跟我还是一对呢
We made out once.
我们还亲热过呢
I never did buy that ring.
我还傻到买了戒指
But we're still..
不过如今我们也还...
close.
很亲近
I have a theory about all this.
我有点想法
That's our cue to bail.
这就是让我们闪的信号了
Tommy Chong here has a theory. Come on,baby.
思想家有所感悟了 来吧 亲爱的
Don't worry,you can tell it to Egghead,here..
别担心 你可以跟那个书呆子好好聊聊
if he's not too busy devirginizing Dana.
要是他不忙着破丹娜的处的话
Jules,do you wanna go lie down?
朱尔斯 去躺会吧?
That's exactly the point. Come on. Mush. Mush.
说对了 走吧 开路 开路
Don't push me around.
别到处推我
Not around,baby. Straight line.
我没到处推你 亲爱的 直线啊
You seriously believe nothing weird is going on?
你没觉得有些事情不太对劲吗?
Conspiracy?
有何高见?
The way everybody's acting.
每个人的表现都不对劲
Why is Jules suddenly a celebu-tard?
朱尔斯怎么突然变得这么放荡?
And since when does Curt pull this alpha-male bullshit?
科特什么时候变得这么目空一切?
I mean,he's a sociology major.
我是说 一个社会学高才生
He's on full academic scholarship...
全额奖学金获得者
and now he's calling his friend an egghead?
管别人叫书呆子?
Curt's just drunk.
科特喝醉了
I've seen Curt drunk.
我知道他喝醉了
Jules,too.
朱尔斯没喝醉吧
Well,then,maybe it's something else.
好吧 除了酒又不是没别的了
You're not seeing what you don't wanna see.
是你拒绝看清真相
Puppeteers.
幕后黑手
Puppeteers?
幕后黑手?
Pop-Tarts?
速食馅饼?
Did you say you have Pop-Tarts?
你说你带了速食馅饼?
Marty,I love you,but you're really high.
马蒂 我爱你 但你真的嗨过头了
We are not who we are.
我们迷失了自我
I'm gonna go read a book with pictures.
我得去找本小人书看看
Thank you. "The pain outlives the flesh.
谢谢 "疼痛超越肉体"
"The flesh returns... "or "has a meeting place."
"肉体回归..."还是"重聚"
What is that?
是什么啊?
The Latin that you read in the basement.
刚才在地下室你读的拉丁文
You speak Latin?
你还懂拉丁文?
Not well. Not since tenth grade.
一般吧 十年级以后就撂下了
Weird how it all comes back.
竟然还记得一些
Well,it's a weird kind of night.
这样的夜晚什么都会发生
I'm sorry about tonight.
今晚真是不好意思
Everybody...
每个人都...
Do I lose points if I tell you I'm having a pretty nice time?
要是我说现在我感觉很好 你不会鄙视我吧?
No. You can tell me that.
不 怎么会呢
What are you running away for?
跑什么呀?
Don't spill on me!
别撒到我身上!
Did I get a little beer on your shirt?
我把啤酒撒你衬衫上了?
I guess it'll have to come off,huh?
那就只好脱掉啦? 对吧?
Not here.
别在这里
Baby,come on.
来吧 宝贝
We're all alone.
这没别人
I'm chilly.
我有点冷
Okay,guys. That's it. Let's go. We've got a job to do.
好啦 兄弟们 到此结束 该干嘛干嘛去
Your basic human needs disgust me.Get out of here.
你们这种低级趣味真让我恶心 赶紧离开这
- Do we have temperature control in this sector? - On it.
- 那个区有温度控制吗?  - 明白
Engaging pheromone mists.
迷人的激素之雾
It's so dark.
太黑了
Take me inside?
我们回去吧?
Come on. This is why we came here.
别这样 这才刺激
It's romantic.
这叫情调
Okay,baby. Let's see some boobies.
来吧 宝贝儿 露出你的胸来
Show us the goods.
来点精彩的
Does it really matter if we see her...
我们这么看她合适吗...
We're not the only ones watching,kid.
小子 不光我们在看
Gotta keep the customer satisfied.
我们得让顾主满意
You understand what's at stake,here?
你得明白 成败在此一举
Score.
得分
Jules
朱尔斯!
This we offer in humility and fear.
带着谦恭与畏惧 我们奉上祭品
For the blessed peace of your eternal slumber.
祝您永眠 祈神赐平安予吾辈
As it ever was.
恰如以往
Nemo,man,you gotta wake up.Your shit is topsy-turvy.
尼莫 哥们 你还是快点醒吧 已经一团糟了
I'm gonna go for a walk.
我还是出去走走吧
Okay. I swear to fucking God,somebody is talking.
好了 我向上帝发誓 有人在说话
Or I'm pretty sure someone is.
呃 真的是有人在说话啊
I'm gonna go for a walk.
我还是出去走走吧
Enough!
够了
What are you saying?
说什么呢?
What do you want?
想干嘛?
You think I'm a puppet,huh?
你以为我是个木偶 啊?
You think I'm a puppet. Gonna do a little...
你以为我是你手里的木偶 想这样跳什么...
fucking puppet dance!
他妈的木偶舞！
I'm the boss of my own brain,so give it up.
我的大脑我做主 别白费劲了
I'm gonna go for a walk.
我还是出去走走吧
I don't wanna...
我不想...
I mean,I've never...
我是说 我从没...
I don't mean "never"...
我不是说永远不...
Hey.
嘿
Nothing you don't want.
我不会勉强你的
He's got a husband bulge.
他勃起了
I thought there'd be stars.
应该有星星啊
We are abandoned.
我们被孤立了
- Fuck!  - Fucking run!
- 靠!  - 快跑!
Curt
科特
Dead bitch!
死鬼婊子!
Jesus,what happened?
上帝啊 怎么了?
The fuck!
操蛋!
- Curt,what the...  - fuck！
- 科特,怎么...  - 操蛋!
Where are you hurt?
你伤在哪了?
Is all of this from you?
这都是你的血吗?
It's okay! Curt,you're okay!
好了 Curt 没事了!
Where's Jules?
朱尔斯人呢?
She's gone.
她死了
We've gotta get out of here.
我们得离开这
No. No.
不 不行
Dana,don't open that...
丹娜 别开门...
I'm not leaving here without Jules.
没有朱尔斯我不走
That dead girl's out there!
外面有个僵尸女!
Dana,come on!
丹娜 来帮忙!
What is that thing?
那是什么东西?
Fuck!
操蛋!
I don't know,but there's more of them.
不知道 不过不止一个
More of them?
还不止一个?
I saw a young girl.
我看到一个年轻的女人
All zombied like him..
都是像他那样的僵尸
but she was missing an arm.
不过她少了只胳膊
Oh,my God. Patience.
噢 天哪 是培先斯
The diary.
那日记
- We gotta lock this place down.  -He's right.
- 我们得把这地方封闭起来  - 他说的对
We'll go room by room. Barricade every window and door.
检查每间房子 堵住所有的窗户和门
We gotta play it safe. No matter what happens,we have to stay together.
必须确保安全 不管发生什么 我们必须待在一起
Fuck!
靠!
Calm down.
别紧张
Watch the master work.
瞧我的手段
This isn't right.
不对
What? What's the matter?
怎么了? 什么意思?
This isn't right. We should split up.
那样不对 我们应该分开
We can cover more ground that way.
这样才能防守更多的位置
Yeah.
好
Yeah. Good idea.
好 好主意
Really?
是吗?
All right,you guys,get in your rooms.
好了 伙计们 回自己的房间去
Lock them in.
锁起来
What the fuck?
怎么回事?
What the...?
这是什么...?
What the fuck?
什么玩意?
That's not good.
情况不妙啊
Out of the way. Out of the way. Out of the way.
让开 让开 让我来
Chem department,I need 500 CCs of Thorazine..
化学部 500CC 氯丙嗪
pumped into room three.
充入三号房间
No,no,no.
不 等等
Stand by,Chem.
化学组 待命
Judah Buckner to the rescue.
犹大・巴克纳来救场了
What the fuck?
怎么回事?
Fuck! What the fuck?
靠! 什么情况?
Oh,my God.
噢 天哪
I'm on a reality TV show.
我上真人秀了
My parents are gonna think I'm such a burnout.
爹妈看到会觉得我是个废柴的
Help me! Help me!
救命! 救命啊!
Must be getting excited downstairs.
下面的有点兴奋了
Greatest show on Earth.
全世界最精彩的演出
Somebody help!
救命啊!
Come on!
快来!
- Use the bed!  - Come on! Come on!
- 用床抵着!  - 快点! 快点!
- It's empty.  - Go.
- 里面是空的  - 走
- Curt?  - Unlock the door.
- 科特?  - 把门打开
I can't. Get down to the basement.
打不开 快去地下室
This is the black room.
这就是那间暗室
Nice.
太好了
From the diary.
日记里提到的那间
This is where he killed them.
他就是在这杀了他们
This is where he kills us.
他也会在这杀了我们
No way. No.
不 不可能
He's not gonna kill us.
他杀不了我们的
We just gotta find a door.
我们得赶紧找到出口
Okay?
知道吗?
Let's just check the walls,okay?
我们还是先查看下四周的墙面吧 好吗?
Curt?
科特?
I mean,there's gotta be...
我是说 这里一定有...
You like pain?
你喜欢痛苦是吗?
How's that work for you?
尝尝这个怎么样?
These fucking zombies.
这些愚蠢的丧尸
Remember when you could just throw a girl in a volcano?
难道他们办事就不能干净利落点吗?
How old do you think I am?
你觉得我只是个三岁小孩?
Let's move! Come on! Come on! Go!
快走! 快点! 快! 走!
What about Marty?
马蒂怎么办?
They got him.
他已经死了
The devil is defeated.
恶魔被打败了
Now Kiko's spirit will live in the happy frog!
基科的灵魂现在将永远活在这只快乐的青蛙里!
Fuck you!
去死吧!
Fuck you! Fuck you! Fuck you!
去死吧! 去死吧! 去死吧!
- You seeing this?  - Perfect record,huh?
- 你看到了?  - 完美的记录 不是吗?
The Japan crew should've had this in the bag. They fucked us.
这本该是板上钉钉的事 小日本真让人失望
How hard is it to kill nine-year-olds?
结果几个九岁大的小屁孩能有多难?
Zero fatality. Total wash.
无一伤亡 纯瞎忙活
You want good product,you gotta buy American.
你想要好产品 那就得买美国货
Any word from downstairs?
楼下有什么消息没?
Downstairs doesn't care about Japan. The director trusts us.
楼下一点也不关心日本 监督者相信我们
You just sweat the chem, Lin.
你把化学部给忙坏了 林
While these morons are singing What a Friend We Have in Shinto...
当这群白痴在高唱我们的日本朋友时...
we are bringing the pain.
我们正在动真格的
Yeah, and what the fuck's up with this guy's pot, anyway?
是啊 但这家伙到底是怎么回事?
He's supposed to be drooling and instead he almost makes us?
他差点就打败我们了 可他不是本应该变成丧尸留着口水吗?
We treated the shit out of it.
是我们太大意了
Okay, we've got the Rambler heading toward the tunnel.
好了 这些家伙已经往隧道去了
The fool's toast anyway.
这群白痴要完蛋了
And so are we if you don't get this under control.
如果你不控制好局面的话那我们也要完蛋了
- Shit.  - What? "Shit" why?
- 该死  - 什么? 什么"该死"?
Gotta go. Work to do.
我先挂了 有活要干
You guys are humanity's last hope. If the ancients rise...
你们是人类最后的希望 如果那些上古邪神复活...
- There's no cave-in.  - What?
- 没有塌方  - 什么?
The fucking tunnel's open!
该死的隧道是通的!
Control to Demolition.
控制台呼叫爆破部
We're dark on the whole sector.
整片区域一片漆黑
Try to bypass it.
赶快搞定
- What the fuck do you think I'm doing?  - Open the door.
- 他妈的你们难道以为我在开玩笑吗?  - 把门打开
Look out!  Get out of the way! Make a hole!
当心! 走开! 别挡着!
- What the fuck's going on?  - We don't know.
- 他妈的出什么问题了?  - 不知道
Electrical said there was a glitch up top.
电力部说上面出了点小故障
- That tunnel should've blown hours ago.  - We didn't get the order.
- 那个隧道几小时之前就应该爆炸了  - 可我们没有接到命令
Hadley, what is going on?
哈德利 发生什么了?
Hadley?
哈德利?
Why hasn't the tunnel blown?
为什么隧道没有爆炸?
No, no. No fucking way!
不 不 不可能!
Can't believe this, man. This ain't happening.
真不敢相信 伙计 这不可能
It's right there.
就在对面
All right. We got any climbing gear? Ropes?
好吧 我们有没有什么攀爬工具? 绳子呢?
Yeah. In my fucking dorm room.
有 在我的该死的房间里
We can't go back.
我们可不能再回去
There's no way across.
根本没路可以过去
What're we gonna do? Jump?
那我们怎么办? 跳过去?
Dude.
老兄
What?
什么?
Curt, are you sure about this?
科特 你确定要这样做?
I've done bigger jumps than this.
再难的我也试过
You've got a smooth run...
你要先稳住...
and maybe a five foot differential on the other side.
对面落差大约有5尺
But you've gotta give it everything.
但你必须要竭尽全力
Curt.
科特
Look, you guys, you stay in the Rambler.
听着 你们俩待在车里
I'll get help.
我去找救援
If I wipe out, I'll fucking limp for help.
就算我挂彩了 我爬也要爬出去求救
But I'm coming back here.
但是我会回来的
I'm coming back with cops and choppers...
我会带着警察和直升机回来...
and large fucking guns, and those things are gonna pay.
还有他妈的重型武器 这些东西都会付出代价的
For Jules.
为了朱尔斯
Don't hold back.
千万别退缩
Never do.
放心吧
No!
不!
Curt!
科特!
Oh, God!
噢 天啊!
He hit something. There's nothing. What'd he hit?
他撞上了什么 可这什么也没有 那到底是什么?
Puppeteers.
幕后黑手
Marty was right.
马蒂是对的
Get in the van.
去车里
Dana.
嘿丹娜
Marty was right.
马蒂是对的
You're going back.
你在往回开
I'm going through.
我在开出去
And we'll just drive. There's gotta be another road.
我们就这样开下去 总会有别的路的
- Another way out of here.  - It won't work.
- 别的出路  - 没用的
Something will happen. It will collapse, it will wash away.
还会有别的事情发生 会塌方 道路会被冲毁
Then we just leave the roads altogether.
那我们就离开这些路
Drive as far as we can into the forest and we go on foot from there.
有多远开多远开到森林然后我们步行离开
You're missing the point.
你没弄明白
Please, do not go nuts on me, okay, Dana? You're all I've got, now.
拜托 别对我生气 行吗 丹娜? 你现在是我的一切
I'm okay.
我没事
Good, okay, 'cause I need you calm.
好的 没事了 因为我需要你冷静下来
Okay, no matter what happens, we gotta stay...
听着 不管发生什么 我们都要保持...
Goddamn, that was close!
该死 就差一点!
Yeah, photo-fucking-finish.
太好了 大功告成
I don't understand.
我不明白
You're celebrating?
你们这是在庆祝?
They're celebrating. I'm drinking.
他们在庆祝 我在喝酒
But she's still alive.
但她还活着
How can the ritual be complete?
仪式怎样才能完成?
The virgin's death is optional, as long as it's last.
处女的死亡是不定的 看她能支持多久了
Main thing is that she suffers.
重要的是她得受折磨
That she did.
她也受了
It's so strange.
真奇怪
I'm actually rooting for this girl.
我开始支持她了
She's got so much heart.
她是如此地顽强
And you think of all the pain and the...
想想她所经历所有的痛苦以及...
Tequila is my lady! My lady!
龙舌兰是我的女神! 我的女神!
Come on in, guys! Come on in. You're welcome.
进来吧 伙计们! 进来吧 欢迎你们
Tequila! From darkness, there is light!
龙舌兰! 黑暗之中总会有光明!
I wish that I could do what you do.
我真希望可以做到你所做的
- Oh, my God.  - Yeah, it's masterful.
- 噢 天啊  - 没错 真是大师级的
I don't know. Tonight was solid. I don't know.
我不知道 今晚不大顺 我不知道
Are you kidding? Classic denouement. When the van hits the lake...
你开玩笑吧? 经典的结局 当车冲进湖里的那一瞬间...
I screamed.
我叫了出来
And the water rushing in, and the zombies...
然后水涌了进来 还有丧尸们...
just think it would've been cooler with a merman.
想象一下 要是有个人鱼怪就更酷了
Do you know if we get the overtime bonus on this one?
你们觉得我们这次能不能拿到加班费?
Accounting's over there. Ask them.
会计就在那 去问问他们
I don't need to. I already know the answer.
不需要 我已经知道答案了
I'm an intern.
我只是个实习生
So I don't qualify for OT.
所以我还不够资格拿加班费
It's funny that you like the ballet..
你会喜欢芭蕾这真是有意思...
because I happen to have two tickets to your favorite...
因为我正巧有两张票都是你喜欢的...
You knuckleheads.
你个蠢货
You almost gave me a heart attack with that tunnel.
隧道那里你差点害我得心脏病
Like I said, it wasn't our fault. We didn't get the order.
我早说了 那不是我们的错 我们根本没接到命令
I'm just giving you a hard time.
吓唬你们的
Come on. Give us a hug.
来吧 拥抱一下
No, seriously. That wasn't our fault.
不 说真的 那真不是我们的错
There was a glitch. Power re-route from upstairs.
出了点故障 楼上的电力线路重接
What do you mean, upstairs?
你什么意思 楼上?
Turn the fucking music off.
把该死的音乐关掉
Hello?
喂?
That's impossible. Everything was done within the guidelines.
不可能 一切都按照指示完成了
The virgin's the only one...
处女是唯一一个...
No. I am not doubting you.
不 我不是在质疑您
Which one?
哪一个?
- Marty.  - Hi.
- 马蒂  - 嗨
Dana, come on.
丹娜 过来
Marty. Wait.
马蒂 等等
We're going in the grave?
我们要去墓里吗?
Dana, come on!
丹娜 快来!
What is this place?
这是哪?
Yeah. I had to dismember that guy with a trowel.
是的 我用泥刀把这家伙给肢解了
What have you been up to?
你怎么样?
Nobody else, huh?
其他人都死了 嗯?
Yeah, I figured.
好吧 我早猜到了
You figured everything.
你全部都猜对了
Oh, not at all.
噢 没有
But, I do know some stuff.
不过 我的确知道一些事情
As in...
就在...
It's an elevator.
这是个电梯
Somebody sent those dead fucks up here to get us.
有人把这些该死的东西送上来杀我们
Now, there's no controls inside, but there's maintenance overrides in there.
那里面没有控制电梯的东西 但这里有个维修装置
And I think I can get it to go down.
我想我能让它下去
Do we wanna go down?
我们真要下去吗?
Where else are we gonna go?
不然我们能去哪?
Come on. Get in.
来吧 进去
Come on!
快来!
Fucking zombie arm.
去他妈的丧尸胳膊
Oh, shit.
噢 该死
We chose.
我们选择的
What? What?
什么? 什么?
Fuck!
见鬼!
All that shit we were playing with.
我们对付的那些东西
They made us choose.
是他们让我们选的
They made us choose how we die.
他们让我们选择如何去死
We saw them go down the access drop. They have to be in one of these.
我们看见他们从入口进去了 他们一定是在这里面
Internal security can.
内部保安人员可以
I don't care if it's not protocol. Are you fucking high?
我可不在乎这是不是符合协议 你他妈的喝多了吗?
It's the fool! Do not touch the girl.
目标是那个白痴! 别碰那个女孩
If he outlives her,this whole thing goes to hell.
如果女孩先死 那这一切就完蛋了
Take him out first.
先把他干掉
Cleanup says the prep team missed one of the kid's stashes.
清洁部门说之前的搜查队漏掉了那孩子的一件藏物
Whatever he's been smoking's been immunizing him to all our shit.
不管他吸的是什么都让他对我们的东西免疫
How does that help us right now? What?
这消息对现在我们还有什么意义? 什么?
No, if you have a confirmed kill, take her out,too.
不 如果你确认男孩已死 把女孩也一起干掉
There.
那里
3606.
3606号
Gotcha.
找到了
Bring 'em down.
把他们带下来
Step out of the elevator! Step out of the elevator!
出来! 从电梯里出来!
- Why are you trying to kill us?  - Step out! Just the girl!
- 你为什么要杀我们?  - 出来! 男的别动!
- What?  - Just me?
- 什么?  - 只有我?
Do it!
快点!
Good work, zombie arm.
干得好 丧尸胳膊
You shouldn't be here.
你们本不应该在这
This should've gone differently.
事情本不应该是这样
Ended more quickly.
这一切早就该结束
I can only imagine your pain and confusion.
我可以想象得出你们的痛苦的困惑
But know this.
但是记住
What's happening to you is part of something bigger.
发生在你们身上的只是一项宏伟版图的部分
Something older than anything known.
这有关于一些最古老的生物
You've seen horrible things.
你们已经见过可怕的东西
An army of nightmare creatures.
一直梦魇恶魔所组成的军队
But they are nothing compared to what came before.
但与之前所发生的事情相比他们都不值一提
What lies below.
这下面所隐藏的生物
It's our task to placate the ancient ones.
我们的任务就是安抚那些上古的生物
As it's yours to be offered up to them.
而你们的使命就是成为祭品
Forgive us.
原谅我们
And let us get it over with.
让我们结束这一切吧
Come on. Go in that room.
快点 进那个房间
Army of nightmares, huh?
梦魇恶魔所组成的军队 嗯?
Let's get this party started.
派对开始吧
Hold fire!
停火!
Oh, shit.
噢 该死
Go! Go! Go!
快! 快! 快!
Lead officer Truman to security command.
指挥官杜鲁门呼叫安全指挥中心
Requesting immediate reinforcements. Code black. I repeat,code black.
请求立刻支援 黑色警报 重复 黑色警报
Where the fuck are you guys?
你们他妈的去哪了?
Sector 12, down. Sector 8,down.
12区 失控 8区 失控
Sector 3, down. Jesus Christ!
3区 失控 上帝啊!
Why aren't the defenses working? Where's the fucking gas?
为什么防御系统不起作用? 该死的气体哪去了?
Something chewed through the connections in the utility shaft.
有东西咬断了接线
- Something which?  - Something scary!
- 什么东西?  - 恐怖的东西!
The north exit is blocked. You can't go there.
北区已经封锁了 你们不能去那儿
Go, go, go!
快 快 快!
Fuck! We're running out of time!
见鬼! 我们快没时间了!
It's on lockdown, I'm trying to bypass.
这里快被封锁了 我正试图绕过去
Hadley!
哈德利!
Oh, come on!
噢 别这样!
It's you.
是你
No, no, no. Please, please.
不 不 不 求你 求求你
Kill him.
杀了他
Okay, Dana, come on.
好了 丹娜 快点
Dana.
嘿丹娜
Here. It's easier with this.
给 拿着这个会好点
Look at these.
看看这些
Five of them.
有五个人
What are they?
他们是谁?
Us.
我们
I should have seen it like you did.
我应该跟你一样都看过的
This is part of a ritual.
这是仪式的一部分
A ritual sacrifice?
献祭仪式?
Great.
很好
You tie someone to a stone, get a fancy dagger and a bunch of robes.
把一个人绑在石头上 拿出一把漂亮的匕首然后 出现一堆穿着长袍的家伙
- Is that that complicated?   - No.
- 有那么复杂吗?  - 不
It's simple.
很简单
They don't just want to see us killed.
他们并不只是想看我们死
They want to see us punished.
他们想看我们受惩罚
Punished for what?
为什么受罚
For being young.
因为年轻
It's different in every culture.
尽管在每个文化力都不一样
And it has changed over the years.
而且随着时光流逝也在渐渐改变
But it has always required youth.
但年轻的生命总是必不可少
There must be at least five.
至少要五个才行
The whore.
那个妓女
She's corrupted.
她已经堕落了
She dies first.
于是第一个先死
The athlete
然后是健将
The scholar.
学者
The fool.
以及白痴
All suffer and die at the hands of...
他们都受过罪并最终死于...
whatever horror they have raised...
自己所挑起的恐惧之手...
leaving the last, to live or die...
至于最后那个 是生是死...
as fate decides.
由命运决定
The virgin.
处女
Me?
我?
Virgin?
处女?
We work with what we have.
我们只有利用好现有的棋子
But what if you don't pull it off?
但要是你不能完成呢?
They rise.
他们会复活
Who does?
谁?
What's beneath us?
我们底下到底是什么?
The ancient ones.
上古邪神们
The gods that used to rule the Earth.
那些曾经统治世界的神们
As long as they accept our sacrifice, they remain below.
只要他们接受我们的献祭 他们就会待在地底
But the other rituals have all failed.
但是其他的仪式都失败了
The sun is coming up in eight minutes.
太阳再过八分钟就会升起
If you live to see it, the world will end.
如果你们能活到那时候 这个世界将覆灭
Maybe that's the way it should be.
也许本来就应该如此
If you've got to kill all my friends to survive...
如果你必须要杀了我的伙伴们才能生存...
maybe it's time for a change.
也许是时候要改变了
We're not talking about change.
我们并不是在讨论什么改不改变
We're talking about the agonizing death of every human soul on the planet.
我们讨论的是人们在这个星球上的生死存亡
Including you.
包括你
You can die with them...
你可以选择和他们一起死...
or you can die for them.
或者选择为他们而死
Gosh, they're both so enticing.
天啊 听上去都挺诱人的
The whole world, Marty.
整个世界 马蒂
Is in your hands, Dana.
都在你手中 丹娜
There is no other way.
没有别的办法
You have to be strong.
你必须得坚强
Yeah, Dana.
是的 丹娜
You feeling strong?
你现在觉得够坚强吗?
I'm sorry.
对不起
So am I.
我也是
Marty.
马蒂
Marty!
马蒂!
Hey.
嘿
You know..
你知道吗
I don't think Curt even has a cousin.
我猜科特根本就没有什么表兄
How are you?
你怎么样了?
Going away.
命不久矣
I'm sorry.
对不起
I'm so sorry I almost shot you.
很抱歉我差点就朝你开了枪
I probably wouldn't have.
我本不该这样
Hey, no. No.
嘿 不 不
I totally get it.
我完全明白了
I'm sorry I let you get attacked by a werewolf and then ended the world.
对不起我让你被狼人攻击然后等着世界末日
No.
不
Hey,you were right.
嘿 你是对的
Humanity...
人性...
It's time to give someone else a chance.
是时候该给其他人个机会了
Giant evil gods.
上古邪神
I wish I could've seen them.
我真希望能亲眼看到他们
I know.
我知道
That would have been a fun weekend.
这本来会是个很有趣的一个周末
--==圣城家园SCG字幕组 http://hd.cnscg.com/==--
协调：心仪
翻译：死神夜月 Mabb Storm89
校对：心仪Sally